hifishark.com 2017-03-06

# Hifishark Privacy Policy

Last updated: December 12, 2016

At Hifishark.com com we take your internet privacy seriously. The purpose of this Privacy Policy page is to communicate our present (at any given time) Policies and Procedures regarding the collection, use, and dissemination of your information. We will not wilfully use, or share your information with anyone, except as described on this page. 

As we develop our business and offer more or different services, we may have to change this Privacy Policy accordingly. In such cases the changes will be posted on this page. Policy changes will be effective immediately upon posting, and the corresponding Procedure changes may come into effect at any time thereafter. 

####  What is collected and why? 

The primary goal of data collection at Hifishark.com is to deliver a well-functioning and attractive Service to our users and to allow third-party providers to do the same. Beyond this goal only the requirements imposed by Danish or European Law are considered. 

####  User provided data 

Some facets of the Hifishark.com service requires the existence of a virtual persona, a Profile, to serve as a link to your real persona, the User. A profile may be established by the association of a Social Network Account (SNA) from either Google.com or Facebook.com, in which case we store the corresponding SNA id and associated email address for future use. Alternatively, a profile may be created by the submission of a validated email account and a password, which we then store for future use. The involved information remains private and is safeguarded by state of the art security measures. 

Once you have a profile, you may chose to provide us further information in order to customise our service. You may, e.g., store search and display preferences, subscribe to Search Agents, or mark listings of interest for future reference. In such cases, we store the given information in association with your profile for your convenience, but it is never shared with, or displayed to, any third-party. 

####  Automatically collected data 

In order to ensure the best possible service we automatically collect data a various levels. At the most basic level, we log the outcome of every page access in order to detect abuse and errors. At higher levels, we track the significant actions of all users for the purpose of analytics, i.e., to assess and improve the effectiveness of the Service and help us optimise your experience. Automatically collected data is not systematically associated with your Profile, but may be taken into account when reported errors are analysed. 

Note, that we may allow third parties, e.g. Google Analytics, to help us collect and analyse information about your use of our service. We do not control the use that such third parties make of the collected information, which instead is governed by their own privacy policies. 

####  Cookies and Advertising 

In order to facilitate your user experience we use a mixture of session cookies (that are never stored on your computer) and persistent cookies (that stay on your computer for a predefined amount of time) to remember your state and preferences. Some cookies are related to authentication and security. They allow you to stay logged in for prolonged periods of time, and help us establish your identity. Other cookies are related to specific parts of our Service, and help us remember your search and display preferences. Hifishark.com does not respond to "do not track" signals, but you can configure most browsers to reject cookies - in this case, however, some parts of the Service may not be accessible to you. 

Furthermore, we may allow third-parties, including [Google](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/), to serve you ads on Hifishark.com and to store cookies for future use. Although we do not provide such third-parties with information that can identify your personally, this use of cookies, including Google’s use of the DART cookie, still enables them and their partners to serve you ads based on your visits to Hifishark.com and/or other sites on the Internet. We do not control whether third-parties respond to "do not track" signals, but you may opt out of the use of advertising cookies, including the DART cookie, by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

####  Forced Disclosure 

Note, that Hifishark.com is subject to current and/or future laws of Denmark and the European Union. As such, we may not be able to ensure that none of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will ever be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, e.g. as part of legal investigations. 

Further note, that even the strong security measures we have in place cannot ensure or warrant the security of your information or provide guarantee against disclosure or loss due to a breach of these measures.
